

# Juan Felipe Rada

### **Frontend Developer**

React, Redux, Tailwindcss, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, SaSS, NGRX

#### OPROFILE

Developer with two years of experiences in Web development.

Passionate about creating and understanding the dynamics of the technology market, Master in Business Digital Strategy.

I am looking for a place where I can combine my programming skills with my experience from the social sciences to improve the products that the client receives.

#### CONTACT

**Phone** +55 (12) 936180526

▼ Email radapls8@gmail.com

**Website** https://radapls.github.io

in LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/radapls

Location São José dos Campos or Remote

#### LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - Professional

Portuguese - Professional

#### HOBBIES

Cooking

Sewing

AR filters

## TOOLS

#### Intermediate professional competence

























#### EXPERIENCE

#### February 2023 - Present

React Developer, NT Consult

Participation in different projects focused on maintaining and improving their web interfaces.

**Development tools:** TypeScript, React, Cypress, Redux, HTTP requests.

#### January 2022 - Present

Frontend Developer, Wiboo Company

Creation of functionalities, maintenance of the state of the web and mobile code.

Management of Planner under the Scrum Agile model for the follow-up of tasks and deliverables. **Development tools:** TypeScript / NativeScript, Angular, Saas, NGRX, HTTP requests.

#### July 2020 - December 2021

Social Researcher, Instituto de Estudios Interculturales

March 2019 - December 2019

**Devlovery Unit Member,** Secretaria de Gobierno, Alcaldia Municipal de Santiago de Cali. ■

January - June 2018

Research Assistant. Misión de Observación Electoral

March - June 2017

**Research Instructor**, Carrera de Ciencia Política, Pontificia Universidad Javeriana Cali. ■

August - November 2016

Research Instructor, Instituto de Estudios Interculturales

#### EDUCATION

#### 2021-2022

**Universidad ICESI -** Master in Digital Business Strategy Emphasis on prototyping and user validation on the different projects. Creation of the SIGET-RB for the management of Telepacfico transportation.

2014-2019

**Pontificia Universidad Javeriana Cali -** Political Scientist Creation of two research seedbeds. Development of design skills